So GPT5 Pro is insane. It's the most
powerful AI model in the world and it
can build essentially anything. Now what
even is GPD5 Pro? It's the best version
of the GPT5 series of models. Believe it
or not, GPD5 Pro has genius level IQ. It
literally scored 148 points on the Mensa
Norway quiz. In fact, this model is so
powerful that it can help you launch a
profitable AI business from scratch,
which is exactly what I'm going to show
you in this video. Now, GPD5 does have a
major problem. Most of the GPD5 models
are not that good because OpenAI was
trying to save some cost. GPD5 Pro is
the only exception. This is the only
model I personally use from the GPD5
family and it's great at coding,
decision-m, reasoning, business problem
solving, anything that involves logic
really. So, in this video, I'll show you
whether GPD5 Pro is worth $200 a month,
how it compares to tools like CL code or
cursor, and how to compete a real $2,000
Upwork listing from scratch using GPD5
Pro to do all of the coding for you.
Now, this model allows you to have
genius level intelligence at your
fingertips, which sounds good on the
paper, but if you think about it, AI is
quickly becoming payto- win, which means
if you're not willing to pay $200 a
month, you do not have access to the
highest reasoning effort. and soon
enough that might be $500 a month or
$1,000 a month. This will inevitably
create a massive divide between the
people who can afford the cutting edge
AI models and everyone else. So the
brutal truth is that you have between 6
to 18 months to get your money up so
that you can comfortably afford these
cuttingedge AI models no matter what the
cost is which ironically will help you
make even more money. Now when GPD5 Pro
runs it was built to think of every
possible solution and that's thanks to
parallel test time compute. This means
that GBD5 Pro runs multiple reasoning
chains at once for each prompt or
question you send it. So instead of
thinking through one possible answer
like most LLMs do, GBD5 Pro explores
several possible ways to solve your
problem all at once. So here's the plan.
We will find an Upwork listing worth at
least $2,000. Using GPD5 Pro, we will
build a project from the listing from
scratch. And at the end of the video,
I'll show you how you can repeat this
process many times to start your own AI
business with just a few hours a week.
And no, you don't have to be a
programmer to do this. So, let's get to
building. Now, if you actually want to
build a profitable business with AI, you
have to understand this one thing, and
that there is no secret. I'm not going
to give you any secret in this video.
Instead, I'm going to teach you a skill
set how to use tools like GPD5 Pro to
solve any problem and turn that into a
side income. So, here is a Upwork
listing that I found. This is a $2,000
listing. Senior AI voice agent, right?
So, we need to figure out what to use
for the AI agent. And then the biggest
second part is the rack. So, basically,
they want to talk with an AI agent via
voice speech to speech. And they want to
have use retrieval augmented generation,
also known as rack with some custom
documents, custom data. What I'm going
to do, I'm going to copy the
description. I'm going to switch to chat
GBD Pro. In the model selector, I
activated GBD5 Pro. I'm going to do
scope. XML tags are great for targeting
model, right? This is really good prompt
engineering tip. I'm going to paste it
in. I'm going to end it with / scope.
That way it's not confused where it
starts, where it ends. The XML tax
clearly show that. So for the voice AI
agent, the best solution right now at
least I think it's the real-time API
from OpenAI and we can implement either
RTC or webockets, but I'm going to leave
that decision to GB5 Pro. So I'm going
to just copy this page. Your task is to
help me figure out how to build this
project as quickly and efficiently as
possible. It is important to follow the
scope, but it's also important that you
do not overthink this project. Boom.
There we go. Right now, if I just send
this, that would be problematic. We
still need to give it a bit more
direction. Where's the next step? Right.
And I would say is to lay out the
structure of this project. So I would
put a clean five-step plan for building
this project. So as you can see the
strategy for prompting GBD5 Pro very
very different than from prompting any
other model to be honest. Why? Because
GBD5 Pro runs for a long time. It can
reason for 10 plus minutes. So you want
to put in the time in the prompt because
if you mess up then you have to wait
until it outputs to send another prompt.
So I'm going to send it. And in the
meantime, I'm not going to waste my time
just chilling and scrolling Twitter.
Instead, I'm going to open up cursor and
we're going to create a project
structure. So, let me open an empty
folder. Boom. There we go. And for the
model, for the spirit of the video, I'm
going to use GBD5. But anyways, GBD5 Pro
has finished reasoning and we have an
answer. It took 3 minutes 16 seconds, so
this one wasn't as bad, but uh let's see
what it said. Use WebRTC. Okay, so it's
going to be Web RTC. So, what I'm going
to do, jump back into cursor and let's
create a markdown file. Boom. New file.
just maind this is like a cursor
markdown style and actually I'm going to
create a folder to do this cursor /
rules and I'm going to move this into
this folder and that's how you do
context engineering within a cursor
right so this is a main file so I want
it to be applied always boom this we
need to have in the main file there we
go but let's look at the first step
right scaffold intra so we're going to
use nextjs with app router for the UI so
this is our front end and for back end
python fast API but maybe we can even
simplify this so what I'm going to do is
I'm going to say create first draft.
Now, think hard whether we can somehow
simplify this plan. This project is not
simple, but it's not complicated. So,
let's not overengineer this. I don't
want to show you just a single
implementation because let's be honest,
whoever watches this video first is
going to just take my implementation and
snipe it. But that's not the point,
right? There is thousands of listings
that are worth thousands of dollars that
you can build with GPD Pro. And if you
watch until the end, the promise I can
make is that you will have the skill set
to do these four figure listings on the
site and launch multiple sources of
income, right? But in the meantime,
let's do some progress, right? Actually,
let's go into cursor. Let's see how it
cleaned up. So, very nice. Look at this.
Formatting is much nicer. So, I'm going
to keep this. And something we should do
with any project is create a new GitHub
project. And we should connect this to
actual repo. So, boom. If you don't have
GitHub account, you must have it. So,
I'm going to name this um AI voice rack.
I know very descriptive name. So, let's
create this repo and then all we need to
do is copy this link, right? Boom. Let's
switch back into cursor. Your task is to
help me connect this project to a new
GitHub repo. Give me the steps how to do
this. Boom. Then I'm going do command J
to open a terminal. So, let's see. So,
we can skip the first command and then
we do get in it to initialize the G
repository. Boom. There we go. You can
see on the right the files are now
unstaged. Then we do get add dot. This
stages all of the files. So if we switch
into this icon, you can see that the
changes have moved from changes to
staged changes. So they're ready to be
committed now. So then we need to do get
commit and write a com message. I'm
going to do the very first comet. So now
we have created this comet. We need to
push it to remote. But since this is the
first time we need to set up the main
branch because GitHub needs to know
which branch is main, right? So that is
get branch- capital M and main. Then
this is the main command, the get remote
add and the URL, right? So this is the
URL to our specific repository. Gator
mode at origin. Boom. There we go. And
then get push and u. This sets upstream
tracking so that in the future I can
just do git push without typing this
whole thing. And boom. There we go. Now
if I refresh here, I should see our main
mdc. There we go. Cursor rules folder.
And we should see the only file we have.
Beautiful. So now when we make progress,
we don't have to worry about AI messing
it up because we can do a commit after
each change. Right? So that's that. This
is very important. Especially if you
want to sell it to the company, right?
No business is going to accept your code
as a Google Drive link. you need to
share them a repository all the file
structure all dependencies history of
comets let's see if we have a response
so it did a simplified the plan very
nice so I'm going to copy the simplified
plan and then I can go into cursor and
again using GP5 fast I'm going to do
remove the current five-step plan from
maindc
file and replace it with this simpler
plan boom so while this is running let's
begin on the first thing so what we need
to do monolith scaffold so this is going
to be our first implementation and I'm
going to just ask ask you to focus on
the first step, right? So, I'm going to
copy it. I'm going say, "Great job. I
like this simpler plan. Now, your task
is to help me fully execute the first
stage." Boom. I'm going to remind it of
the first step. And I'm going to say,
"Take a deep breath and proceed like a
senior developer would. I want you to
give me the full execution of the first
step, which means the complete file
structure. Show me the file tree and as
well as the full code for each of the
files for the first step."
Overengineering is perhaps the biggest
danger we can do. So let's keep it to a
quick and dirty prototype. Okay. So
again, I'm using my voice to prompt
engineer faster. Boom. And notice the
previous prompts were more like
planning. Now it's execution. But now
the real fun begins. Now we're actually
building the project. So let me accept
this simply plan. Looks great. And then
what I'm going to do is say great job.
Let's stage this file and push to
GitHub. There we go. So it did
everything here. We should see two
comments right here. There we go. So now
we can use cursor agent, the chat agent
to do the comments for us. So I don't
have to type the comm of what was
changed. Since it will know that it will
save us time, right? Okay. So GPD5 Pro
has finished reasoning and we have the
first stage entirely done. So what we're
going to do is scroll to the bottom.
Copy this whole thing. And I'm going to
say your task is to implement the
following stage one into our codebase.
Okay. And then I'm going to stage one
XML tags. Paste the whole thing in.
Close the stage one. Boom. Most of these
I think cursor agent can do for us. So
let's see. We're going to use GPT5 fast
for this. Let's launch it. And again,
the beauty of this business model is
that you only have to complete like four
or five of these jobs a month to reach
$10,000 a month, which is just
incredible. I mean, it has never been
easier to start making money with AI.
And by the way, what I'm showing you in
this video is just a taste. It's just a
sneak peek of what we have in the New
Society classroom. In this workshop
right here, you'll learn step by step
how to start your AI business, how to
get the first paid client, how to start
taking on bigger projects, getting more
leads, building predictable revenue and
scaling to $10,000 a month and beyond.
There are hundreds of people in the new
society who have made their first
dollars with AI. In fact, I'm so
confident in this business model that if
you follow these steps and you don't
make any money within 6 weeks, I will
personally refund you your money back,
no questions asked. So if you're serious
about AI and want to start your own AI
business, click the link below the video
and join today. All right, let's jump
back into cursor. Let's see what was
done. So we have a new folder right here
with the file structure. Pretty simple.
Let's see. So we have five new files
created. Okay. And then we need to
install the requirements to run it
locally. Let's see if there's any manual
step in the first stage that we have to
do ourselves that cursor cannot do for
us. So after big changes, you always
should push to GitHub. So I'm going say
stage all files and push to GitHub. We
can review the changes, but I don't
think that's necessary. You can see that
some of these dependencies are
underlined. That's because we don't have
them installed in our cond environment.
So, I'm going to do env list. And
actually, I'm going to create a new
environment for this in and you know
what? I'm going to show you again how to
problem solve, right? So, I'm going to
say list out all of my env.
And then, assuming you've never created
a new conv environment, you can just
ask, how do I create a new condens?
Let's name it Upwork and use Python
3.12. Actually, do we have a Let's match
that with with Okay, 3.11. So, yeah, we
need to match that with GP5 Pro. Tell me
what to do step by step. Answer. Just
answer. Okay, answer in short. Boom. And
in the meantime, we can actually get GB5
Pro started on the next stage, which is
stage number two. Docs plus rag. And
what should I do? U one thing I'll use
repo prompt. This is a great tool for
because you know the problem is that
GBD5 Pro is available inside of SH GBD.
So we have to copy paste it. That's
inefficient. With repo prompt, we can
load up this folder. Boom. Code. And
here's our repo with everything. Right.
So I can just select the whole thing and
I can say I've completed stage one. Your
next task is to help me fully execute
stage two. I'm going to paste it in here
as well. Boom. This is the step. Doc
plus rag. Let's see if we need to do any
web search for this. Store uploads under
extract. No. This seems seems pretty
simple. I mean, I don't know how to do
it, but it's pretty simple for GBD5 Pro.
You know, the smartest AI model in the
world. I'll say take a deep breath and
proceed like a senior developer would.
Make sure to complete stage stage two
fully and completely. Do not do anything
else. Output all all of the code files
in full and give me clear and concise
instructions on what to do. Okay. So,
now we can see at the bottom this is
3.6,000 tokens. That's nothing. So I'm
going to copy our entire codebase and
we're going to go back into JGBT5 Pro.
Let's go to the bottom. I'm going to
paste it in. And now it's going to work
on stage two with the context of stage
one being completed. So repo prompt
allows us to load in the entire file
structure. The entire code base into a
single prompt and send that to GP5 Pro
which again is necessary because OpenAI
has only made it available inside of
JBD. Oh, let's uh let's fix this issue
of dependencies being underlined by
creating a new cond environment. I'm
going to name it Upwork because this is
the this is the business model we're
doing. You know, just claiming Upwork
listings with the most powerful model in
the world. And again, there's only so
much time before this strategy gets
saturated. Like same with drop shipping,
same with Tik Tok shop. Every single
business model gets saturated sooner or
later. So realistically in about 6
months everybody will know about this
and amount of people doing this will be
100x more than it is now. So if you are
looking for an opportunity do not wait.
We are still very early to AI and not
many people know that models like GBD5
Pro even exist let alone how good they
are. So if you want to start on this
strat start today. Anyways so we've
created the environment. Next up we need
to do cond activate upwork to activate
the environment. And then we just double
check the version. Python- version
should say 311. There we go. Beautiful.
So, inside of cursor or VS code, doesn't
matter what code editor you're using,
below my webcam right here. Here you can
see the version. That's because this is
not activated. So, we need to activate
the Upwork environment. Let's type in
Upwork. Boom. And this is the Python
interpreter. And once we run the pip
install requirements, this should
disappear. So, let's open the terminal.
Command J again. And actually, you know
what? Let's not do that. Let's do the
easier way. I'm just going to tell the
agent to do that. Okay, I've done this
and I activated the cond environment.
Open up a terminal. Make sure this
Upwork environment is active and then
install the requirements.txt. Everything
that you need to do, you can get the AI
to do. All you need is initiative. If
you have initiative and if you have a
bit of intelligence to problem solve,
you can use AI to learn anything, to
solve any error, to build, to scale your
business, right? All you need to do is
ask the right questions and keep
working. Do not quit. As long as you
don't give up at the first error, you're
going to be fine. So, let's see. We
install the requirements and there you
go. The dependencies are no longer
underlined, which means we've solved
that issue. Let's see how GVD5. Okay,
it's still reasoning. It's still
thinking. That's fine. In the meantime,
we can actually check if we've done
everything from stage one.
So, I'm going to scroll back up and
actually for okay, this is this is an
idea I just got right now for
organization because scrolling is
inefficient. I'm going to create a new
folder and actually no, we can put it in
the rules folder. I'm going to create a
new file. I'm going to do answer-01
MD, not MDC. And this is going to be
just the answer from chat GBD so we can
easily reference it. I'm going to target
read answer01.
Is there anything else we have to do
manually
or is it fully completed?
Pink heart
answer in short.
Boom. There we go.
Let's see at the bottom. Okay. GBD5 Pro
is still reasoning. It's fully
completed. Okay. What about the env
file? Because we have a ENV example and
we might need to add the opening API
key. Surely
I have to provide the OpenAI API key
myself.
Read the ENV file. I think cursor
actually doesn't have access to this.
You can see the Yeah, it's disabled in
cursor ignore. Okay, I need to stop it.
I need to provide it. Here's what it
looks like. Yeah. So, this is one thing
for security reasons. Cursor doesn't
have access to ENV files, which is good.
It's a good security practice, but you
just have to know it as a beginner and
you have to realize, okay, we'll have to
provide it. And if you need to show it,
you need to paste it in. Right now,
since this is an example file, we need
to create an actual env file. So, I'm
just going to copy paste it and rename
it to env.
There is nothing after the main ENV file
is env. And the only thing we need to
get is the open API key, which is super
simple. Just type in open AI API key
into Google. Click the first link. This
is going to take you to OpenAI platform.
Here you need to log in with the same
account you use for Chad GBT. There we
go. I'm logged in. So on the left, click
on API keys, then create new secret key.
I'm going to name it Upwork business
model. Boom. Create secret key. Copy. Do
not share your API keys with anybody.
Okay? Keep them private. Treat them as
passwords. I'm going to delete my key
before uploading this video. It's a very
important security practice. And do not
commit them. Right? This is very
important. We could say I created this
env file. Make sure our git ignore
properly
ignores it. Okay, you cannot commit them
to GitHub. This is one of the biggest
mistakes beginners make is they commit
their env files into GitHub and if it's
a public repo, anybody can access it and
use your API key and steal your credits,
right? And lose your money. So, let's
see. I'm verifying whether ENV is both.
So we can actually open git ignore and
we have it in here. Beautiful. So on the
staging on the right even though we
created a new file it's not in the
changes. So it is being ignored. So we
can safely do a commit. Say good work.
Let's do another GitHub push documenting
this. So even though this will be not
saved, I want to do a push because we
have some changes. We created the
markdown file that the answer is one
complete. And actually I'm going to be
more specific. I'll say that um the
first stage of main
has been completed. So we want to
document that. And for as for these
those should be fine. What we can
actually do is double check what the
model should be. Actually we're probably
using it from the official docs. So that
should be fine. Need a model 25. Yeah
this is the official. Okay. Just quick
double check. It never hurts to check
the docs. That's fine. So there we go.
It's push. So what's the issue? Push
dog, you need to be in the root folder.
So the the problem is that it was in the
AI dental voice folder. So that's
whatever small thing. There we go. So
now we're squeezing GB5 Pro. You can see
the reasoning time is going up, which
means more and more compute is going
towards our project, right? There we go.
So what I'm going to do, scroll all the
way to the bottom again. I'm going to
copy it, jump back into cursor, and then
create a new folder. I mean, new file in
this folder, answer-02.md.
Boom. Paste it in 750 lines. Okay.
Anyways, I'm going to say next, I need
you
to fully implement the following changes
for stage two. Do not rewrite any of the
code. Just implement the following files
exactly as they are. Boom. I'm going to
do stage two. Paste it in very long
prompt. Stage two, I say take a deep
breath and proceed like a senior
developer would implementing these steps
properly and exactly as they are. Do not
change anything. Do not do anything
else. There we go. So now cursor is
going to execute and implement whatever
GBT 5 Pro suggested. We might need to
add some stuff. Okay, embedding model.
We need to add this to our ENV file. So
I'm just going to copy this.
Boom. add it below right here. Save
that. Let's see. Let's scroll back up
just quickly. Take a look at it. So here
we have some new code files fully
implemented. Cursor is just going to
actually edit our codebase, right? So
it's not going to change anything
because this is the most powerful AI
model. We don't want this to be
regenerated. We have updated file tree.
So we need some new files here. Okay,
beautiful. Clearly documented. And yeah,
that should be it. So copy your env to
env set setup API key. We need to run
this again. We need to start our back
end. We need to open up the local host.
That would be interesting. So let's do
that. Okay. So I can do the terminal
with command J. Let's reinstall the
requirements txt again. Boom. We don't
have Okay, we need to first cd into this
folder. So the way to do that, you can
do ls to see all your folders right in
that directory and do cdai dental voice.
Boom. that we can see now we are in this
folder. Beautiful. So I'm going to clear
the terminal again and I'm going to run
it again because we don't we don't have
the requirements txt in the root. We
have it in this folder. Right. So that
was the issue. What do we need to do
next? We need to start u server which is
just a way of start starting a fast API
service. Let's start it. There we go. We
have a bit of lag but there it is. And
we it's running on this URL. And we have
an error. No module name nonpie. So, I'm
going to kill the server with Ctrl C.
Let's we'll we'll figure out what
happens once u once the cursor agent
finishes implementing things.
So, nump we need numpy
where let's do numpy.
Okay, there it is.
Embedded text. Okay, so maybe for the
rag. Interesting. We'll see. We'll fix
that. No problem. In the meantime, let's
see what we need to do. We need to run
the docker for phase. This is the rag
library we're using. Okay, so to be
super efficient, we should honestly get
started on stage three. Here we're going
to solve a small box inside of cursor
that's faster because uh it doesn't do
as much reasoning as GP5 Pro. So cursor
has implemented everything. Let's see
what's happening. So it created new
files, made some edits, some changes
invamp.
Okay, edit app rag. Okay, so we need to
install dependencies again. So let's
press up a few times. There we go. Oh,
there it is. Numpai is being installed.
Okay. So I just run that command a bit
too early. So now if we start the
uicorn, we should have the app working.
So we can go to this URL. Let's see what
happens. Okay. Here we have our app.
The voice agent is here. Start. Okay. So
open API key is not set even though it
is.
Let's check that.
It is set.
Maybe it's not being properly
referencing. Whatever. We're going to
debug this. I just want to get started
on the stage three. So again, repo
prompt. I'm going to refresh. So
everything is loaded. I'm going to load
the entire codebase. Now it's 15,000
tokens. So it's growing. And I say I've
completed stage two. Your next time is
your next step is to complete stage
three. Boom. Here's stage three. Voice
agent wiring. And actually for this what
would be good
is to get the latest docs again from
OpenAI docs. Let's copy that. I'm going
to say OpenAI docs. Boom. Paste it in /
OpenAI docs.
We could actually even add it to our
codebase. Maybe that's better.
Boom. New file. I'm do real time
API MD. Just paste the docs in here.
And now we can easily tag it. We can
delete it from our prompt here because
we're going to tag it as a file. Okay.
So, let's uh again refresh
in the cursor rules folder. Let's select
this as well. There we go.
I'm going to say take a deep breath and
proceed like a senior developer would.
Output all of the files, all of the code
files in full and give me step-by-steps
instructions on what to do. Let's copy
that as a full prompt. 20,000 tokens
back into CHIGBT. Paste that in. In the
meantime, let's begin debugging some of
our issues. So, we can actually uh keep
all. We don't have to click through it.
But yeah, so we get we get an error
here.
We get an error internal server error.
Now, we have the error message
that is not looking at the open API key.
So I'm going to say when I click start I
get this error. Okay. I'm also copy the
terminal also. Here's the terminal
output. Explain to me why this error is
happening and then analyze the three
most closely related files and propose
to me a simple and clear theory as to
what is causing this error and how to
fix it. Do not do anything else. Just
answer in short. And actually in the
meantime we should probably commit the
stage two to GitHub. So I'm going to
show how to do that. So first we do get
add dot to stage all the files. Let's
double check there is nothing sensitive.
We should be file. Maybe the docker file
is questionable. Whatever. Let's do git
commit m stage to completed and get
push. Very simple. We don't have to use
AI for that. We can do it while the
agent is responding. Okay. So our server
was started before the ENV was loaded.
Wow. Okay, let's kill the server and
let's restart it. In the main, I'm going
to do I'm going to do a server start
command. Just document it in here. We
have it. That's how you build your
internal docs. Let's reload this.
Connection is connected. Start
connecting. Okay, there we have it.
Allow microphone. So, allow while
visiting this site. Test. 1 2 3 4. Do
you hear me?
Okay. So, it's responding.
>> Can you speak in English?
>> Of course, I can definitely speak to you
in English. What would you like to talk
about?
>> Perfect. So, tell me who you are.
>> Sure. I'm an AI assistant here to help
you out with information, answer
questions, or just have a friendly chat.
Let me know what you need and I'll
>> Amazing. So, the voicetovoice agent
works right now. Of course, this UI
could be better, but we're not focused
on fancy UI. Anybody can do that. You
can build a fancy UI with like two
prompts in Lovable, right? It's not
impressive anymore. What's impressive is
building working full stack apps that
actually solve a real problem such as
this problem, which is or this company
is worth $2,000, right? And again, we
have a voicetovoice agent. This is
already way better than you cannot build
this in any vibe coding app, right? But
you can easily build this with GBD5 Pro.
So let's test the documents, right? Is
document upload working? Uh or is that
actually that's the next step, right?
Voice agent wiring. I mean, this already
works. This already works. So I'm going
to say read main and tell me what's left
because the speech
to speech already works. Does the agent
have access to the docs we upload or is
is that just empty UI in the front end?
Bing hard answer in short. Let's see. So
in the meantime, we can actually test it
to be honest. So what I'm going to do,
okay, GBD5 pro reasoning. I'm going to
get a PDF
and upload it here. Right. So boom.
Let me see if we can drag it over.
We can. Beautiful. So, this is the GBD5
system card. GBD5 system. Let's do
upload and index.
Will this work? Okay. The UI is a bit
clanky. Let's see.
Dun left. Wire the voice agent to rag.
Okay. So, this is this is still hasn't
been done. So, okay. Beautiful. So,
voice to voice agent works. Obviously,
again, the UI is UI is not clean, but it
works guys. That's the main thing. We
can clean up UI easy. That's the easiest
part, right? AI models are amazing at
front end. The real part is like
building a full stack app that actually
works. That's the hard part. And we have
a voicetovoice agent using OpenAI
real-time API. And we're about to add
the rag now. GBD5 Pro is cooking.
Amazing. So, what can we do here? Uh, in
the meantime, maybe we can clean up the
UI. I mean, to be honest, I like this
minimalist UI. It almost like I think I
I predict there's going to be a meta of
reversing to the previous you know the
previous simpler UIs like everybody's
doing these gradients and all that
stuff. I think people are tired of that.
People can spot an AI generated user
interface fast. So I predict more and
more apps will have simpler UIs. Maybe
I'm wrong but that's just my prediction.
We have the document here. We see the
file. So it is uploaded. It is indexed
into 89 chunks using the phase library.
We can actually we can actually do rack
search as well. So let's do uh tell me
about GBT 5 thinking pro. I think that's
the name. RA model search. Let's see if
the search works. That Oh, it works.
Look at it. GB5 system card chunk 57.
Okay, let's do thinking. There we have
it. We have the thinking references.
Okay, so this is this is what um vector
databases are all about. You know, I
asked about GB5 thinking pro and it's
finding the chunks that are the closest
semantically to this, right? So, here we
have reference of GB5 thinking pro
and yeah, we we have another one right
here.
Beautiful. Amazing. So, we have working
rack in this app on top of the voice to
voice. We just need to connect them
together. That's the next stage. That's
what GBD5 Pro is working on. You can see
guys, this this didn't take a week. Like
I I'm literally building this for like a
bit over an hour and we have something
that if you did this manually would take
you many days assuming you know what to
do, right? If you don't know what to do,
it would take you multiple weeks. But
thanks to using the most powerful AI
model in the world, GBD5 Pro, you can
actually build these full stack projects
even if you've never used these before,
right? I've never built this project
before. I I have no clue how to build a
senior AI voice agent with rag knowledge
database for dental. I have no clue. But
I can ask the smartest AI in the world
and I can build it. And again, this is
worth $2,000. And as I said, it has
never been easier to get to $10,000 a
month with AI. Forget about starting an
agency and doing all these mainstream
models. This is the real untapped
opportunity using the most powerful
coding agent in the world to deliver
these medium level projects. I mean,
these are not simple, but they're not
complex either, right? medium difficulty
projects and just build them as a side
thing, as a side hustle and deliver them
to the client, right? It's pretty
incredible what time we live in. And
there we go. So, GB5 Pro reasoned for 8
minutes. Notice how the time is slowly
increasing as the complexity is
increasing. And there is stage three.
So, in our classic fashion, let's go to
the bottom. Can click this button. Copy
it. Boom. cursor new file answer-d
boom paste it in I'm going to say next
your task is to fully implement the
contents of answer 03
into our actual codebase proceed like a
senior developer would boom let's switch
back to JGBT see what what we need to
implement ourselves because there's
always something that AI cannot do.
Uh seems like we need to again reinstall
the requires txt. That's fine. We are
already used to that. And uh we should
be good. We don't even need to start the
docker. Real time with ephal tokens is
recommend browser pattern. Okay. Okay.
So let's see how cursor is proceeding.
Okay. It's currently going to replace
some of the files, make some of the code
changes. Man, I'm telling you guys, this
is a untapped opportunity. I'm not just
speaking out of my ass.
This is a reason why I chose this
business model in the new society,
right? I've seen people try hundreds of
different things and some of them are
way too difficult. Some of them it's
hard to make money. This one is the
perfect balance, right? Again, it won't
take you one day, but in the matter of
six weeks, you can go through this
workshop. You can focus on setting up
your tech stack in week one. In week
two, getting your first paid client in
week three learning how to do bigger
projects. And again for all of these
using GBD5 Pro to help you get unstuck.
You don't have to be a programmer. You
don't have to be an entrepreneur. You
don't need any previous business
experience. All you need to do is have a
few hours a day to to follow these
steps. If you follow these steps, you
will see results. And again, if you
don't, I'll personally give you the
money back. No questions asked. That's
how confident I am in this business
model. It really is amazing what you can
do in 2025 with AI. And it has never
been easier to start a business with AI
yet so few people are taking advantage
of it. Perhaps that is the saddest part.
Most people are not doing nothing. I
mean we might we have literally genius
IQ level AI models and most people are
still not doing anything about it which
I guess um that's just human nature. I
don't know. Anyways, let's let's see if
cursor is struggling or if it finished.
It finished. Okay.
So then let's reinstall requirements
txt. Boom. Open up the terminal. Command
J. I'm going to kill the server with
Ctrl C. Clear. Reinstall this guy.
Everything has been installed already.
And then we run our command
to load the ENV file as well. Unicorn
Unicorn command. Boom. There we go. And
what else? Nothing. We just need to
refresh the server. So, let's do that.
Reload the server. We need to Okay, we
have the file already indexed. That's
beautiful. So, we can start asking
questions about it probably. Let's Let's
see if this works. Okay. Yo, can you
hear me?
>> Yeah, I can hear you loud and clear.
What's up?
>> Do you see the PDF document I attached?
>> I don't see any PDF document right now.
Could you try re-uploading it or
describing what's in it? I'd be happy to
help either way.
>> Okay, I'm uploading it right now. I just
uploaded it. Check your tools. Do you
have access to it?
>> I still don't see anything on my end.
Maybe the upload didn't go through.
Could you double check and try sending
it again? Or just give me a quick
summary of what you need help with from
the document. I'll do my best to assist.
>> Listen, do you see the GPD5 system card?
>> I don't have visual access to any system
card or document right now.
>> Yeah. So, that's the last missing piece
connecting the voice agent to the rag
because both of them work separately,
right? We've seen the rag work
perfectly. We've seen the voice agent u
work. The way I would solve that is with
perplexity, right? So what I would do is
I would say
uh I I would probably copy this. I'm
going to say app boom
app.
I've toggled on the DB research and I
say I have built this entire app. I have
the open AI real-time API working. The
AI voice agent can successfully do
speech to speech and also the rag is
working. The last remaining piece is
figuring out how I can connect the PDF
files and documents to the OpenAI
real-time API. How I can feed in these
documents to the AI agent that is
running with the real-time API. Browse
the web and give me a detailed
step-by-step instructions how to do
this. Now again, we can use GBD5 Pro and
we will. The reason I'm doing a
perplexity DB research is because I want
to have the latest documentation for
this. Then I'm what I'm going to do is
I'm going to feed that into GPD5 Pro and
fix this one last piece because that's
all that remains. And again in the repo
prompt we should refresh. Boom. Let's
select the whole codebase. 27,000
tokens. Now I'm going to say everything
is working. The speechtoech
functionality works and the rack qu I
can also ask questions with the rack.
The last missing piece is making sure
that the AI voice agent has access to
the documents that it can actually
reference them when I'm talking with it.
Below is the official documentation that
you need to follow. Boom. I'm going to
give it docs and that's going to be the
output of the perplexity DB research.
There we are. So, this is checking lots
of different sites. Okay, it's going to
be like this. Paste it in there. Your
task is to analyze the entire codebase,
find where the issue is, and fix it so
that the voice agent during the
speech-to-pech conversation can
successfully reference any of the
attached documents and talk about them.
Make sure to output all of the updated
code files in full and then tell me step
by step what to do. All right, so the
prompt is prepared. We just need to
paste in the docs. So perplexity
research is searching all the docs and
you get you see this is exactly the
process like if you get stuck at
anything just do a perplexity search or
even chd research doesn't matter and
then use GBD5 pro to solve that problem.
If it's a smaller problem it's faster to
just solve it inside of cursor right but
for anything like you're struggling with
anything you get stuck throw it in GPD5
pro and it solves it. It's that
powerful. This is this is the most
powerful reasoning model in the world
that you know it runs 5 minutes, 10
minutes, but it's worth it. It's worth
it waiting that. So, I'm going to copy
this. Boom. Repo run. Paste it inside.
Copy the whole thing. 29,000 tokens.
Switch back to GBD5 Pro. Send it in. And
in about 5 to 10 minutes, I'll have a
response and I'll have this MVP of this
app fully completed. And again, we can
clean up the front end. I have dozens of
videos that show that. That's the easy
part. What I wanted to show you is the
problem solving part, the hard skills,
right? Using real-time API, which
personally I've never built with this
before, right? I don't know. I've just
feed it in to GB5 Pro. It built it for
me. This listing was created a few hours
ago. So again, I've had no way of
preparing for this. But if, as you can
see, I have the problem solving skill
set. I can use the AI to solve anything.
And I really believe that there's no
problem I can cannot be solved.
Sometimes it might take breaking it down
to smaller steps and you know working in
stages but it doesn't matter with AI you
can solve anything and you can
absolutely build a side hustle AI
business that you know is like a
multiple sources of income for you if
you already have a job or it's just a
side hustle that you can upkeep with a
few hours per week. It's up to you but
you can absolutely do it especially with
the help of the best most powerful AI
reasoning model in the world. And
hopefully this video shows as a proof of
that. All you need to do is solve
skills, clearly describe the error
you're facing, clearly describe the
problem, and use the tools that are
already available, guys. GBD5 Pro,
cursor, perplexity, vectal, all of these
tools already exist. You don't have to
reinvent the wheel. You just need to
apply them. And that's why I structured
it into this workshop into the six week
program so that you literally don't even
have to think. You can just follow these
steps. If you get stuck, ask GD5 Pro. Do
a proxy research and proceed like that.
So again, if you're serious about AI,
make sure to join the new society. In
here, you'll learn step by step how to
build your first AI business and scale
it to $10,000 a month, even if you are a
complete beginner. It's going to be the
link, first link in the video. With that
being said, thank you guys for watching.
Let me know if you want more videos on
GBD5 Pro. It's a very powerful model.
And I wish you a wonderful, productive
week. See you.